<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<BLOG>
    <STORY>
        <TITLE>Garmin</TITLE>
        <DATE>1/13/2014</DATE>
        <IMG_URL></IMG_URL>
        <TEXT>Hello! This is my very first post... it also happens to be the night before a big interview so I'm going to keep this short.
        Today I flew for the fourth time in my life. I left out of Minneapolis and arrived in Kansas City. Thankfully, I do not suffer the same pain in my ears as my father does, otherwise the miracle that is flight might not seem as amazing as it always does. Anyways, once I landed I procurred the rental car, a Chevy Sonic, Garmin graciously provided for me (they are paying for my whole trip down). Utilizing a Garmin GPS (go figure) I managed to find the Fairfield Inn and Suites by Marriott. As usual, my room is great and very comfortable. The bed looked so comfy I almost passed out, however I needed to stay awake a bit longer so that I could find someplace that sold travel shaving cream as I wasn't able to bring my large tube of it down. I went to the local Walmart and looked around. Not finding any travel sized shaving cream, I looked for other options. That's when I found it: Luxury Shaving Soap. I have no idea how well it works, but it sounded fancy and interesting, so I bought it.
        Well, as I mentioned before I have a big interview tomorrow, so goodnight! Cheers to hoping Luxury Shaving Soap works well!</TEXT>
    </STORY>
    <STORY>
        <TITLE>Garmin Day 2</TITLE>
        <DATE>1/14/2014</DATE>
        <TEXT>So I made it to my interview without any hickups! I'm actually proud of that because 1) I've never been to Kansas before and 2. I've never been to Kansas before (but really, finding everything on my first try when I'm at a location for the first time is nice). Honestly though, I cannot take all of the credit. I had that wonderful Garmin Dashboard GPS helping me out. The facility was also only 4 miles from my hotel...
        Skipping around, the building itself is fairly impressive. Coming in at arounda capacity of 3100 people (I think), it's definitely not the largest building I've been to, but it sure isn't the smallest. As I was a visitor, I thankfully recieved parking in the visitor section which was relatively close to the part of the building I was going to. Relatively speaking because it sure was a lot closer than the PARKING GARAGE employees can use. Once inside, I noticed they have a very nice lobby showcasing some of their products and employees. The people also seemed friendly right off the bat. After a little bit of waiting, I interviewed with two very nice ladies from HR. After the standard questions (and some I haven't recieved before i.e. order these terms in accordance to job importance: finance, security, challenge, learning, location) I was taken to a Process Engineering Manager. After talking for quite some time, he brought me to the Plant Manager and I interviewed with him. Oddly enough, the Plant Manager had actually worked 20 years ago at the same company I interned for three years ago (Preco Inc.). Once we were both done with questions, I went to lunch with the Process Engineer in the building's cafeteria. Over lunch, we discussed a lot of excercise related topics, such as how we both used to wrestle and what we are currently doing for workouts. I found this fitting as Garmin appears to be a very active and fit company to me, and I recall having heard that they are 3rd in some statistic for being the healthiest workplace (ref?). Anyways, after that I recieved a plant tour and another interview and then was done (the plant tour was really cool, but I don't necessarily know if I can talk about it).
        I was shown the door on good terms, returned my rental car with no issues, and was on the plane early. After sitting down, the man next to me and I started talking. A few minutes into the converstation we started talking about my schooling. He then hands me his business card and suggests that I send him my resume! That's just a lesson that opportunities can arrise when you least expect them to I suppose. The rest of the flight was uneventful: read some words in a book, took some sweet pictures, and drank free ginger ale.
        And that's really the end of anything exciting...</TEXT>
    </STORY>
    <STORY>
        <TITLE>OSI a.k.a. Open Systems International</TITLE>
        <DATE>1/17/2014</DATE>
        <TEXT>So I had another interview today... and I should really have written this earlier and when I'm not in bed (it seems to be a trend for these posts so far).
        Driving up to the location, I really had no idea what to expect. I did not expect to see a beautiful, modern building tucked away in Medina, Minnesota. I was even more surprised when I walked in. Apparently, the style is something called "Mid-Century Modern", which means it was what people in the 50's and 60's thought the future would look like. All I can say is, I wish they would have been more right as I love that style (or, at least what OSI's architects created out of it). I think I can honestly say I was more nervous for the OSI interview than I was for Garmin, and I put most of the blame on the ominous sounding technical interview test portion. I don't want to complain too much, as I feel like any kind of preparation will probably help in the long run, but I definitely stressed way too much for that test. Not that I'm saying it was easy, it just wasn't as deathly hard as I had thought it was going to be. Anyways, after that the tours and interviews and other assesments went off without too much hullabaloo, so there really isn't much to talk about that might be interesting to the two people that might read this. Some other random notes: the interview was on a Saturday, there was 9 people interviewing, and it was from 10am-2:30pm, and my friend and I accidentally arrived an hour early.
        Oh, one thing that might be of interest is what OSI actually does. Again, to prepare myself for the interview I read through most of their website... What I learned at the interview day was far more helpful. To be brief, they make the software runs in big control rooms for utilities companies. Picture the computer setups in mission control centers from movies, and then you'll kind of have the right thing in mind. If you want a better explanation, try looking them up... because... it's late...</TEXT>
    </STORY>
    
</BLOG>